<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<!DOCTYPE bugzilla SYSTEM "https://bugzilla.redhat.com/bugzilla.dtd">

<bugzilla version="4.2.4-7"
          urlbase="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/"
          
          maintainer="bugzilla-requests@redhat.com"
          exporter="rsmeral@redhat.com"
>

    <bug>
        <bug_id>891949</bug_id>
          
        <creation_ts>2013-01-04 10:43:00 -0500</creation_ts>
        <short_desc>Inaccuracies in Resolved Issues for Seam in 5.2.0</short_desc>
        <delta_ts>2013-01-25 07:28:42 -0500</delta_ts>
        <reporter_accessible>1</reporter_accessible>
        <cclist_accessible>1</cclist_accessible>
        <classification_id>5</classification_id>
        <classification>JBoss</classification>
        <product>JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 5</product>
        <component>doc-Release_Notes</component>
        <version>5.2.0</version>
        <rep_platform>Unspecified</rep_platform>
        <op_sys>Unspecified</op_sys>
        <bug_status>ON_QA</bug_status>
        <resolution></resolution>
          
          
        <bug_file_loc></bug_file_loc>
        <status_whiteboard></status_whiteboard>
        <keywords></keywords>
        <priority>unspecified</priority>
        <bug_severity>medium</bug_severity>
        <target_milestone>---</target_milestone>
          
          
        <everconfirmed>1</everconfirmed>
        <reporter name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</reporter>
        <assigned_to name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</assigned_to>
          
        <estimated_time>0.00</estimated_time>
        <remaining_time>0.00</remaining_time>
        <actual_time>0.00</actual_time>
          
        <qa_contact name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</qa_contact>
        <cf_fixed_in></cf_fixed_in>
        <cf_show_homepage>---</cf_show_homepage>
        <cf_cust_facing>---</cf_cust_facing>
        <cf_internal_whiteboard></cf_internal_whiteboard>
        <cf_devel_whiteboard></cf_devel_whiteboard>
        <cf_doc_type>Bug Fix</cf_doc_type>
        <cf_release_notes></cf_release_notes>
          
        <cf_build_id></cf_build_id>
        <cf_story_points>---</cf_story_points>
          
        <cf_verified>FailedQA</cf_verified>
        <cf_clone_of></cf_clone_of>
          
          
        <cf_environment></cf_environment>
          
          
          
        <cf_type>Bug</cf_type>
        <cf_regression_status>---</cf_regression_status>
        <cf_mount_type>---</cf_mount_type>
        <cf_documentation_action>---</cf_documentation_action>
        <cf_crm></cf_crm>
        <cf_verified_branch></cf_verified_branch>
          
        <cf_pgm_internal></cf_pgm_internal>
          
          
          
          
        <target_release>---</target_release>

      
        <token>1361131017-103ab25297b5911e46c603c14e215e2a</token>

      

      

        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5327828</commentid>
            <who name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-04 10:43:14 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Document URL:
                http://documentation-devel.engineering.redhat.com/docs/en-US/JBoss_Enterprise_Application_Platform/5/html/Release_Notes_5.2.0/ch04.html

                Section Number and Name:
                Seam/Seam2, https://issues.jboss.org/browse/JBPAPP-8322

                Describe the issue:
                The formulation is not right towards the end: 
&quot;...lookup from user applications and Seamspace examples...&quot;
                The Seamspace example is not mentioned in the issue at all, the issue pertained to multiple examples: mail, quartz, seambay and seampay (as stated in one of the comments). 

                Suggestions for improvement:
                The text should either list the affected examples or just say &quot;...lookup from user applications and Seam examples...&quot;

                Additional information:
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5328229</commentid>
            <who name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-04 12:57:02 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Several other issues found in the same document, in the same section (Resolved Issues for Seam):

                JBPAPP-7183:
                The sentence
&quot;This update ensures that when an empty path is detected, &quot;/&quot; is set as the cookie value.&quot;
                is incorrect, it should state &quot;...&quot;/&quot; is set as the cookie path&quot;.

                JBPAPP-8465:
                The RN text contains the text &quot;cgilib.jar&quot; (with an extra &quot;i&quot; as the third character). Correct is &quot;cglib.jar&quot;.

                JBPAPP-8376:
                The RN text for this issue seems superfluous, because the failure of the Seambay ftest happened only because of JBPAPP-10075. So, the RN text currently describes JBPAPP-10075. Also, it is inconsistent in this sentence: 
&quot;When a SOAP message did not contain the element and was processed by the SOAPRequestHandler, the processing failed with a NotLoggedInException.&quot;
                The NotLoggedInException is not related to the SOAPRequestHandler itself, it is just a result of the broken SOAPRequestHandler, specific to the Seambay example. I think this RN should only briefly state that the Seambay now works, because JBPAPP-10075 was fixed. JBPAPP-10075 has a RN in the same section anyway.

                JBPAPP-10075:
                It would be clearer if the phrase &quot;..so attempts by the Seam web service to process...&quot; used an indefinite article: &quot;..so attempts by a Seam web service to process...&quot;. 

                JBPAPP-7201:
                The first sentence is unclear in saying &quot;...interfaces in the Seam Component were...&quot;. It should say something like &quot;...interfaces of a Seam component...&quot;. Also, the sentence &quot;This data structure does not guarantee the order of local and remote business interfaces, which resulted in the order being undeterministic.&quot; is a bit clumsy. There&apos;s no relation between HashSets and business interfaces, so something like &quot;This data structure does not guarantee the order of elements, thus the order of business interfaces was nondeterministic.&quot; would sound clearer. Finally, the correct class is java.util.LinkedHashSet, not java.util.LinkHashSet.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5341024</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-08 18:37:09 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Attention: Ron

                Regarding JBPAPP-7183, please confirm what the cookie&apos;s value is set to if an empty path is detected. I&apos;m a little confused when you have written:

&quot;...&quot;/&quot;

                Please also review the JIRA comments for this issue. Marek Novotny suggests a significant change to the Release Notes&apos; text.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5341064</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-08 19:17:42 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Attention: Ron

                Regarding JBPAPP-8376, could you please review the latest 2 comments by Marek Novotny on this issue? Those comments seem to conflict with what you stated in comment 1 above. I am not able to confirm which is the more technically accurate and from that determine what the issue&apos;s Release Notes text should be.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5341073</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-08 19:29:25 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Status quo:

                JBPAPP-8322 - COMPLETE
                Text changed to &quot;...lookup from user applications and Seam examples...&quot; as per Ron&apos;s advice in this ticket&apos;s description.

                JBPAPP-7183 - NEEDINFO
                Waiting on feedback from Ron, as per comment 2 above.

                JBPAPP-8465 - COMPLETE
                I looked at the latest revision of the document on docstage and couldn&apos;t confirm this issue. It may have been corrected in the meantime.

                JBPAPP-8376 - NEEDINFO
                Waiting on feedback from Ron, as per comment 3 above.

                JBPAPP-10075 - COMPLETE
                Text changed as per Ron&apos;s excellent feedback.

                JBPAPP-7201 - COMPLETE
                Text changed as per Ron&apos;s excellent feedback.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5342861</commentid>
            <who name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-09 04:43:49 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Re: JBPAPP-7183
                There&apos;s a bit of a mix up between issues JBPAPP-7183 and JBPAPP-7269. They are both related to bugs in &lt;s:token&gt; (even in the same class ClientUidSelector), but JBPAPP-7183 talks about an issue with the cookie _path_ being empty and JBPAPP-7269 deals with illegal characters in the cookie _value_. However, changesets for both of these issues are mistakenly referring to JBPAPP-7183. That&apos;s also the reason for Marek&apos;s RN text proposal being so different -- it refers to JBPAPP-7269. 
                I think the RN text for JBPAPP-7183 is OK, if we just fix the problem with the forward slash -- currently it says, paraphrasing: 
&quot;If the cookie *path* is empty, the cookie *value* is set to forward slash&quot;
                Correct would be:
&quot;If the cookie *path* is empty, the cookie *path* is set to forward slash&quot;
                What I missed, however, is that the JBPAPP-7269 is missing in the Release Notes Resolved Issues. 
                Even though these issues are related to the same class, they still fix different problems and thus should be mentioned separately, I think.


                Re: JBPAPP-8465
                If I check http://documentation-devel.engineering.redhat.com/docs/en-US/JBoss_Enterprise_Application_Platform/5/html/Release_Notes_5.2.0/ch04.html doing a complete refresh (bypassing cache, seeing the other changes you made) I still see &quot;cgilib.jar&quot;. Just to make sure we understand each other: It is a Code Generation Library, so just CG Lib -- cglib.jar (just one &quot;i&quot; in the word).


                Re: JBPAPP-8376
                The problem here is that these 2 issues: JBPAPP-8376 and JBPAPP-10075 describe the same underlying problem, even the RN texts of both describe the exact same problem: the SOAPRequestHandler didn&apos;t add the header to a message that did not contain it and thus processing of a message failed. Now the header is added.
                My suggestion was to make JBPAPP-8376 RN text state only that it happened due to the underlying issue JBPAPP-10075, which was fixed.
                I do not find so important the fact that the whole discussion about the underlying problem (JBPAPP-10075) happened in JBPAPP-8376.
                I reviewed Marek&apos;s comments and to make this clear, I&apos;ll rephrase the points I tried to make in my first comment:
                1. The RN text is superfluous (but still valid), because it describes something that is already described elsewhere (the RN text for JBPAPP-10075)
                2. I found the RN text a little confusing, because it made it sound as if the SOAPRequestHandler raised the NotLoggedInException. I find the RN proposal by Marek Novotny in his last comment in JBPAPP-8376 correct, he especially tries to remove this confusion (emphasis mine): &quot;...processing may fail with a Exception, IN CASE OF SEAMBAY example with a NotLoggedInException...&quot;.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5365777</commentid>
            <who name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-15 12:33:45 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>I&apos;ve been reminded there&apos;s another problem with several of these issues, specifically JBPAPP-8465, JBPAPP-8376, JBPAPP-10075 and partly JBPAPP-8322. These are all related to the forward compatibility of Seam2 with EAP6, but this is not mentioned in these release notes.

                JBPAPP-8322:
                This RN already contains a mention of EAP6 in the first sentence, which is OK. However, the last sentence mistakenly mentions EAP5. The last sentence should say (change marked with *): &quot;The respective transaction lookup was added to EAP 5 Seam so that transaction lookup from user applications and Seam examples now works as expected *also on EAP 6*. &quot;

                JBPAPP-8376:
                Again, we need to mention that the described behaviour pertains only to EAP6 and not to EAP5. Assuming we agree that this issue should only refer to the underlying JBPAPP-10075, as described in previous comments, the RN text should say something like:
&quot;The Seambay example failed the functional tests on EAP 6, throwing a NotLoggedInException. This was caused by the underlying issue JBPAPP-10075, which was fixed in this release.&quot;

                JBPAPP-10075:
                Add mention of EAP6 plus fix a mistake (remove the word &quot;function&quot; after &quot;SOAPRequestHandler&quot;):
&quot;The Seam web service integration uses the SOAP header for storing the conversation&apos;s ID. However the SOAP header is not mandatory *and in EAP 6 it&apos;s no longer present by default*. Therefore any attempts by a Seam web service to process a message without a header failed. To resolve this issue the SOAPRequestHandler now adds a header to any message where the header is missing.&quot;

                JBPAPP-8465:
                Mention of EAP6:
&quot;The Spring example application failed to run *on EAP 6* because the *cglib.jar* file was signed. This has now been resolved by un-signing the file and the example now runs *also on EAP 6*.&quot;
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5437226</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-21 21:19:26 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>JBPAPP-8322
                I changed the last sentence to read: &quot;The respective transaction lookup was added to JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 5 Seam so that transaction lookup from user applications and the Seam examples now works as expected also on JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 5 and 6.&quot;

                Is this revision correct?

                JBPAPP-8465
                I changed &quot;cgilib.jar&quot; to &quot;clib.jar&quot;.
                I also changed the product references as so: &quot;The Spring example application failed to run on JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 6 because the &lt;filename&gt;cglib.jar&lt;/filename&gt; file was signed. This has now been resolved by un-signing the file and the example now runs on JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 5 and 6.&quot;

                JBPAPP-10075
                I have made the changes proposed above (in Comment 6).

                JBPAPP-8376
                I have replaced the existing text with the text proposed above (in Comment 6).
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5437268</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-21 21:41:27 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>JBPAPP-7269
                I have now added a Release Notes entry for this JIRA issue, in the &quot;Seam/Seam 2&quot; section.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5437371</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-21 22:21:34 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>I have made all the requested changes. The amended revision is available at [1]. When validating this change, please confirm that you&apos;re viewing revision 25 or higher.

                http://documentation-devel.engineering.redhat.com/docs/en-US/JBoss_Enterprise_Application_Platform/5/html-single/Release_Notes_5.2.0/index.html
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5439230</commentid>
            <who name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-22 09:01:26 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>It&apos;s almost correct now, just a few more notes:

                JBPAPP-8322:
                Basically OK, but it would be even clearer, if the wording was as proposed.
                Your reformulation says: &quot;... works as expected also on JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 5 and 6.&quot;, which makes it sound as if it had never worked before neither on EAP5 nor EAP6. That&apos;s not true. This has not been an issue with EAP5, it worked OK there. It has only now been ammended (not really &quot;fixed&quot;) in Seam2 (which is distributed as part of EAP5 and certified to work with EAP6) so as to work also with EAP6. So I propose again, either: &quot;...now works as expected _on both_ JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 5 and 6.&quot; or the original wording &quot;...now works as expected also on JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 6.&quot;

                JBPAPP-7269:
                The description of the fix given in the last sentence is wrong. Using decodeHex and encodeHex methods was only suggested by some user in the JBSEAM-4503 issue, but it has not been accepted. The changeset is here: https://source.jboss.org/browse/Seam/branches/enterprise/JBPAPP_5_0/ui/src/main/java/org/jboss/seam/ui/ClientUidSelector.java?u=3&amp;r1=11218&amp;r2=14292
                By looking at org.jboss.seam.util.RandomStringUtils, it can be seen that -- and this should be the last sentence of the RN text -- the issue is fixed by only allowing letters and numbers to be a part of the cookie value.
                Sorry for not mentioning this information earlier.

                JBPAPP-10075:
                I insist on including one important part you seem to have dropped -- the emphasis that the SOAP Header is no longer present *only in EAP6*. Again, this issue has surfaced only due to the migration effort of EAP5&apos;s Seam2 to EAP6. So due to some changes (the lack of SOAP header by default) in behaviour of EAP6 (most likely the JAX-WS implementation), this became an issue for Seam2 applications running on EAP6. Therefore, I suggest reverting the sentence
&quot;However the SOAP header is not mandatory and no longer present by default.&quot; 
                to 
&quot;However the SOAP header is not mandatory and in EAP 6 it&apos;s no longer present by default&quot;
                or some *grammatically or stylistically* more appropriate form thereof.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5448844</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-24 16:36:06 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Attention: Ron

                The EAP 5.2.0 GA date is today so I can&apos;t make any further changes as yet. However I will make this amendement and have a corrected revision of the Release Notes made available within the next working day or so.

                I have therefore changed this ticket&apos;s status to &apos;Assigned&apos; as it&apos;s now my responsibility.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5449347</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-24 18:03:11 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Attention: Ron

                Another issue requires me to change and re-release the EAP 5.2.0 Release Notes so I will correct these issues immediately. I&apos;ll update this ticket again when the amended revision is available.
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5449435</commentid>
            <who name="Russell Dickenson">rdickens@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-24 19:02:09 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>I have made all the requested changes. The amended revision is available at [1]. When validating this change, please confirm that you&apos;re viewing revision 101 or higher.

                http://documentation-devel.engineering.redhat.com/docs/en-US/JBoss_Enterprise_Application_Platform/5/html-single/Release_Notes_5.2.0/index.html


                Ron: Can I please check something. Regarding JBPAPP-7269 you said &quot;the issue is fixed by only allowing letters and numbers to be a part of the cookie value&quot;. However when I look at the code you linked to, the function in use is named &quot;randomAscii&quot;. If it&apos;s randomly selecting ASCII characters, couldn&apos;t it still select a semicolon (as an example only) and therefore still create a cookie with an invalid value?
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5450851</commentid>
            <who name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-01-25 07:28:42 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>JBPAPP-7269:
                In the linked changeset red lines are removed, green lines added. So the call changed from randomAscii(50) to random(50, true, true). I verified the correct behaviour in a one-off covering this issue a few weeks ago, it is definitely OK: https://issues.jboss.org/browse/JBPAPP-10456?focusedCommentId=12740080&amp;page=com.atlassian.jira.plugin.system.issuetabpanels:comment-tabpanel#comment-12740080

                JBPAPP-10075:
                Just a typo:
&quot;JBoss Enterprise PLatform 6&quot; (missing &quot;Application&quot;, capital L in &quot;Platform&quot;)
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
      
      

    </bug>
    <bug>
        <bug_id>911617</bug_id>
          
        <creation_ts>2013-02-15 08:41:00 -0500</creation_ts>
        <short_desc>Problems with testing of DeltaSpike quickstarts</short_desc>
        <delta_ts>2013-02-15 08:41:39 -0500</delta_ts>
        <reporter_accessible>1</reporter_accessible>
        <cclist_accessible>1</cclist_accessible>
        <classification_id>5</classification_id>
        <classification>JBoss</classification>
        <product>JBoss Enterprise WFK Platform 2</product>
        <component>Examples</component>
        <version>2.2.0</version>
        <rep_platform>Unspecified</rep_platform>
        <op_sys>Unspecified</op_sys>
        <bug_status>NEW</bug_status>
        <resolution></resolution>
          
          
        <bug_file_loc></bug_file_loc>
        <status_whiteboard></status_whiteboard>
        <keywords></keywords>
        <priority>unspecified</priority>
        <bug_severity>unspecified</bug_severity>
        <target_milestone>---</target_milestone>
          
          
        <everconfirmed>1</everconfirmed>
        <reporter name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</reporter>
        <assigned_to name="Karel Piwko">kpiwko@redhat.com</assigned_to>
        <cc>bsutter@redhat.com</cc>
    
        <cc>rruss@redhat.com</cc>
        <estimated_time>0.00</estimated_time>
        <remaining_time>0.00</remaining_time>
        <actual_time>0.00</actual_time>
          
        <qa_contact name="Karel Piwko">kpiwko@redhat.com</qa_contact>
        <cf_fixed_in></cf_fixed_in>
        <cf_show_homepage>---</cf_show_homepage>
        <cf_cust_facing>---</cf_cust_facing>
        <cf_internal_whiteboard></cf_internal_whiteboard>
        <cf_devel_whiteboard></cf_devel_whiteboard>
        <cf_doc_type>Bug Fix</cf_doc_type>
        <cf_release_notes></cf_release_notes>
          
        <cf_build_id></cf_build_id>
        <cf_story_points>---</cf_story_points>
          
          
        <cf_clone_of></cf_clone_of>
          
          
        <cf_environment></cf_environment>
          
          
          
        <cf_type>Bug</cf_type>
        <cf_regression_status>---</cf_regression_status>
        <cf_mount_type>---</cf_mount_type>
        <cf_documentation_action>---</cf_documentation_action>
        <cf_crm></cf_crm>
        <cf_verified_branch></cf_verified_branch>
          
        <cf_pgm_internal></cf_pgm_internal>
          
          
          
          
        <target_release>---</target_release>

      
        <token>1361131017-c2ae1b79a4d5a54dbfddf0a5e550ab13</token>

      

      

        <long_desc isprivate="0">
            <commentid>5511659</commentid>
            <who name="Ron Šmeral">rsmeral@redhat.com</who>
            <bug_when>2013-02-15 08:41:39 -0500</bug_when>
            <thetext>Description of problem:
                There are multiple issues with testing of DeltaSpike quickstarts.

                1. example-settings.xml and README
                Described in https://issues.jboss.org/browse/JDF-206.
                Also, in the WFK quickstarts README:
                - Section &quot;Configure Maven&quot; (EAP6), point 1: the formulation &quot;unzip every Maven repository zip file into a directory of your choice.&quot; is quite unclear. If it&apos;s supposed to mean, that all of the repositories (EAP, WFK) should be unpacked into one directory (effectively merging the repositories), it should say something like &quot;unzip the Maven repository zip files into one directory&quot;
                - changes may need to be made to the mirroring settings in settings-wfk-example.xml, if the jboss public repository would be included.

                2. MavenDependencyResolver
                https://issues.jboss.org/browse/JDF-207
                Taking into account the changes above (adding repo http://repository.jboss.org/nexus/content/groups/public, changing mirroring to &quot;*,!central-eap6,!central-eap6-plugins,!jboss-public-repository-group&quot;), tests for quickstarts that use MavenDependencyResolver (at least deltaspike-beanbuilder, deltaspike-deactivatable, cdi-add-interceptor-binding) still don&apos;t work. Even though they build OK, the MavenDependencyResolver can&apos;t get DeltaSpike dependencies, which implies, that it can&apos;t access central (which might be a problem of MavenDependencyResolver itself).

                3. deltaspike-deactivatable
                This quickstart depends on 1.0.3.Final version of the JBoss BOMs, which is mosty likely incorrect, as all the other distributed quickstarts depend on 1.0.4.Final-redhat-1.

                4. deltaspike-helloworld-jms
                This quickstart depends on Weld SE, which is not a supported technology in WFK. 

                Version-Release number of selected component (if applicable):
                2.2.0-DR1
            </thetext>
        </long_desc>
      
      

    </bug>

</bugzilla>